*************************************************
	- These are bench tests for testing a naive implementation of a collision handler versus an optimized version. Essentially, both must use a "pass" system; in both systems, a single pass will test any possible collisions that are occurring and process those collisions. Since sprites may move around when collisions occur, if a sprite is moved, multiple passes will be necessary. Note that when I talk about movements of Sprites in collisions, I am referring to a position reset: resetting a Sprite to a previous x or y position that would cause the collision to no longer occur.

	- Naive Implementation: Test each sprite versus every other sprite to see if there's a collision. If any collisions occur that involve moving a sprite at all, all collisions will need to be checked again between all sprites. Because we are checking every collision between each sprite we have a big-O runtime of O(n^2) and a big omega runtime of Ω(n^2), where n is the total amount of sprites in our SpriteHandler.

	- Optimized Implementation: First sort all sprites based on their left-most x point of their CollisionArea. This will take at most O(n*log(n)) time, underneath we are using MergeSort, which in reality will take much less time since most of the Sprites are not moving very much in between cycles, so the SortedList will stay in pretty much the same order.
	Now we start at the beginning of the SortedList and check each Sprite against its next right neighbor, if that neighboring Sprite is out of the range of the current Sprite, then we are done checking collisions for that sprite. Out of range is defined as a neighbor's left endpoint x being further right than the right endpoint of the Current Sprite. This would mean that there is no possible way for a collision to occur and since all the other Sprite's after that neighbor have left endpoints that are greater than or equal to that neighbor's left endpoint, they too are incapable of colliding with the Current Sprite.
	If a collision does occur and it doesn't involve any movement of Sprites, then continue checking collisions until you are out of range. If a collisions occurs and some movement of either Sprite occurs, remove the resetted Sprite(s) from the SortedList and re-insert them (in sorted order O(logn)) at the beginning of the next pass.
	Using this method of collision handling, we can make a single pass in worst case O(n^2), which will occur when all Sprites are overlapping all other Sprites (a rare occurrence, but possible depending on your game). However, our best case is now O(n), due to the fact that if no collisions are occurring, we only need to check every Sprite against its neighbor which is O(2n) or just O(n). In practice, this will help speed up collision handling, since the fewer collisions we have, the shorter our single passes will be.

	- Also, take note that more optimizations are in place for making passes shorter as well, such as checking optimal collision areas and skipping non collidable Sprites. For these tests we are just focusing on the Naive implementation versus Optimized implementation runtimes; both have the same deeper optimizations as well, so these will affect runtimes, however the ratios between naive and optimized will remain intact.