*************************************************
	- These are bench tests testing an optimization added to the Collision Handler to switch between X and Y sorting in the Sprite's Sorted data structure. A decider function is used to choose which comparator will be used next: X or Y. This decider function (decideNextComparable()), finds the variance (standard deviation is unnecessary as it is just an extra step) of all the sprites in the X and Y directions. It uses those variances, and chooses whichever axis has the larger variance; the rationale being that a larger variance means that sprites are more spread out and should therefore have less collisions in those directions.
	- These tests will range in a spectrum from broad to narrow. In broad applications, X will be the dominant variance, since there is more space to run in the X axis. The same goes for narrow applications and the Y axis. The only issue occurs when we have a world that is as broad as it is narrow, as we will need to be switching from X and Y as the variances will generally be very close.
	- Before any bench testing, it is worth noting that using a CollisionHandler that automatically chooses the best axis, removes the burden of choosing an axis from the developer. In most games, we will be dealing with broad or narrow worlds, in which case the collision handler will always choose either the X or Y axis. However, if the overhead of switching between the two in a square world is too much, more fine tuning will be necessary. Essentially, we will need a way of determining that the variances are of a significant difference that we should switch, and not just switch when one is slightly better than the other.